Marina Kozak

QA Engineer

Location: Brest, Belarus Salary expectations: negotiable Mob. +375 (44) 732-32-05 (A1) www.linkedin.com/in/marinakozak7 (LinkedIn) marinakozak7@gmail.com (E-mail) marinakozak7 (Skype)

PROFILE

I'm a QA Engineer with approximately 1 year's experience in testing. In addition, I have rich expertise in translation, and a degree in Linguistics and Tourism Management. If you're looking for an attentive to detail and a hardworking specialist, please feel free to reach out to me.

SKILLS

- Expertise in manual testing of web, mobile, Salesforce based apps using different types of testing (functional, smoke, critical path, extended, regression, cross-browser, cross-platform, UI/UX, localization, exploratory, API testing).
- Review, analysis and clarification of requirements with BA, PM, Developers.
- Creating and maintaining up to date test documentation (checklists, test scenarios).
- Bugs reporting and tracking.
- Understanding of SDLC, client-server architecture, and deep knowledge in software testing theory.
- Ability to write simple SQL queries.
- Foreign languages English (B2), Turkish (A2), Spanish (A1).

WORK EXPERIENCE

August 2021 — March 2022, Manual QA Engineer, SolbegSoft

Projects: SteelCase, a web application with a base of building materials for furniture finishing. OtherMe, a cross-platform mobile application, which represents a social network for the US healthcare workers.

July 2021 — August 2021, **QA Trainee**, SolbegSoft

Projects: *MedScan*, a cybersecurity solution for hospital's medical devices.

May 2021 — June 2021, Salesforce QA Intern, JET BI

Projects: Advantage, a CRM-embedded competitor analysis tool.

2010 — 2019, **English and Turkish Translator**, Dialect Ltd.

EDUCATION

Software Testing course by Vadim Ksendzov, https://ksendzov.com/, 2021

Software Testing Introduction training by EPAM Systems Inc., 2019

Software Testing course by IT-school myIT, 2019

Tourism manager, Institute of Continuing Education at BSU, 2012

Cross-cultural and communication specialist, English and Turkish interpreter, MSLU, 2009